It's amazing!
It's so cute!
My bangs are...
Suda-eki!
I'm the real Suda-eki!
This program is a program where six
people work to advertise something
exciting and go on a rampage in the
world with various things.
I'll challenge all the things I want to
do
I'll prove my exciting future
Happy New Day!
Good morning!
What's this applause?
I don't know.
Today is the first live performance of
Shintarou.
Finally, this day has come.
Yes, it's here.
We finally got to celebrate this day.
We were supposed to have a concert in
April, but it's been about 3 months.
I'm glad we could have a concert this
year.
I was a little worried about whether we
could do it this year.
I'm really happy that we were able to
celebrate this day.
And the set is amazing!
It's amazing!
I was surprised.
I'm not on stage, but I'm watching it
on the monitor.
It's LED.
I'm looking forward to it.
I would be happier if the fans were
there.
But we will do our best to show our
full power through the live broadcast.
We will do our best not to lose to the
set.
I got it on.
Thank you.
This is the first live performance of 6
people.
It's a live performance, so we can only
do it live.
I saw Seito's face just now.
It was amazing. It was so cute. I'm
looking forward to it.
Yes. Bye bye.
I'm wearing a hair accessory!
I put on lipstick and it's done.
It's a little low.
It's a low-cut twin because it matches
my hair style.
I'm going to do my bangs.
My bangs are going to be good from now
on.
I'm going to put on makeup.
If I'm wearing Tomorrow's outfit, I'm
wearing a bun.
I'm wearing a skirt.
I'm wearing a solo dress.
I have bangs.
I'll do my best.
I got my hair done!
I usually wear half-tween for this
costume,
but I'm wearing it to match the next
costume.
So, it's easy!
I'm WANNABE's chubby, chubby Aki-chan!
I'm Aki-chan!
I'm Suda Aki!
I'm the real Suda Aki!
Where is the ball?
Oh, cool!
You are so cute!
Are we practicing?
Go, go, go!!
Thank you very much.
Whattt?
Beyond that!
So cool!
You are great!!
Here I take it
You are so cute!
I drew it!
Thank you!
I am drawing the bamboo swatoon!
The last chorus is my part. I'm so
nervous.
Who scored nothing?
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
I can't take my eyes off you
I want you to find me, you who look
like you're going to die
I want to run from today and go home
I'll do it from the bottom of my heart
I'll dash, dash, dash to the top of my
heart
I'll say goodbye to the sweet energy
I'll say goodbye to the sweet love
I'll say goodbye to the unyielding
happiness
If I do it today,
Shake off, shake off, shake off, shake
off
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Together, Tomorrow!
The strongest sense!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Together, Tomorrow!
The strongest sense!
Well, here we go!
I don't need a sign to start a game
I'll go to you faster than anyone else
Is it love? Is it love?
I'll put my soul into my maiden heart
I'm sorry for pretending to be weak
I'm a little bit shy, but I like you
Is it love? Is it love?
I don't need a sign to start a game
Let's calm down, let's calm down
Think, think
Concentrate, concentrate
It's impossible, it's impossible
The overflowing freedom is lonely
Stop it, stop it
Let's take a little detour
Yes, let's go to that park
Let's buy a Pikachu at the vending
machine
I'm so excited! I'm so excited!
I'm the most excited!
I'm the most energetic!
I'm the queen!
Everyone's choosing, right?
I want the best combination!
If our eyes meet, we'll be in a perfect
line!
I'm so excited! I'm so excited!
I'm the queen! I'm the queen!
These bodies people
These legs people
just keep calling
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Let's go! Tomorrow!
The best!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Let's go! Tomorrow!
The best!
Just being here makes me happy
This kind of time is happiness
A rainbow-colored adventure
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Let's go! Tomorrow!
The best!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Go! Go!
LIVE TO MAKE ARSENAL
I say, the victory declaration!
Listen up! Listen up!
I don't know what the limit is
But let's start by conquering this
country
I'm number one!
I'll always be waiting for someone
I remember the days I spent with you
Even if I try drinking the juice I
liked
It seems a little too much for one
person
Even now, I have a lot of fun memories
Shining in the sparkling sky
I tried to reach out with both hands
I tried my best, but
I'm sure I can't reach you anymore
I like you
I miss you
Every time I think of you like this
The back of my chest is tight
The rainbow-colored bench
I'm still waiting
The white bench
The scenery that made my heart flutter
I'll always be waiting for someone
You're not coming back here anymore
I was able to say, I'll do my best,
I'll do my best
Stay by my side a little longer
I love you, I love you
Hey, I'll never forget
Under the sky with one eye open
I love you, I love you
I love you
I'm happy just being like this
This kind of time is happiness
A rainbow-colored bench
Will never change
Benji! One, two, six, nine!